Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Eeny. meeny. miny. moe
Catch a tiger by the toe
Eeny. meeny. miny. moe.
Here I am.
Maybe I should've picked the 1st floor.
What's going on?
Oh my God!
This is gonna be fun!
It's so lame.
I want a full-length mirror.
A slip. a silk one.
A mattress.
And a blanket!
A microfiber one.
And a portable toilet too.
No more to spend!
So food and drinks are provided.
What about a table?
Protein.
Iron.
Perfect.
How pretty!
Your expressions are so funny!
"Funny"?
We just learned that the prize money
for each room is different.
Everyone should share theirs.
How much do you all get?
For me.
80.000 won a minute.
You get 80.000?
I get 30.000 won.
-20.000 won.
-130.000 for me.
Wait. What is this?
Everyone's is different?
And you. 7th Floor?
How much do you make a minute?
I get 210.000 won.
And 8th Floor
should get exactly 340.000 won.
How do you know?
Did you just calculate the numbers
in your head?
No. If you think about the prize money
going from the 1st to the 8th floor.
there's a pattern.
If you add the two preceding numbers.
you get the next one.
1st Floor said he gets 10.000 won.
2nd Floor gets 20.000.
Yes.
You're right.
Yes. Add those two numbers.
and you get three.
That's why 3rd Floor
is getting 30.000 won.
Yes. it's 30.000 won for me.
I'm right above 3rd Floor
on the 4th floor.
so if I add 2nd Floor's 20.000
and 3rd Floor's 30.000. yes.
I get 50.000 won.
Wait. I'm getting 80.000 won. so…
That's the sum of 3rd Floor
and 4th Floor's prize money.
Then the next floor--
6th Floor's is five plus eight.
which is 130.000 won.
The same goes for me.
and I get 210.000 won.
That's how 8th Floor gets…
340.000 won.
Yes. that's right.
It's the Fibonacci sequence.
I've heard of that.
But what does it have to do
with our prize money?
Why does it apply here?
I wouldn't know the hosts' intentions.
but they seem like an interesting lot.
The Fibonacci sequence
creates a golden ratio.
-A golden ratio?
-Yes.
In a Fibonacci sequence.
if you divide a number
by its preceding number.
the ratio converges to approximately 1.6
as the numbers increase.
This 1 to 1.6 ratio
is called the golden ratio
because. for humans.
it provides a sense of security
and is perceived as beautiful.
For example. the ratio
of a credit card's dimensions
is close to the golden ratio.
Coincidentally. the floor cards
we picked up on our way in…
Are the size of a credit card.
But isn't this unfair?
This was all random.
This is really fucked up.
You're the ones who picked them.
Stop whining.
and let's take a look at everyone's rooms.
8th Floor gets 340.000 per minute.
489.6 million won a day.
7th Floor gets 210.000 per minute.
302.4 million won a day.
6th Floor gets 130.000 per minute.
187.2 million won a day.
5th Floor gets 80.000 per minute.
115.2 million won a day.
4th Floor gets 50.000 per minute.
72 million won a day.
3rd Floor gets 30.000 per minute.
43.2 million won a day.
2nd Floor gets 20.000 per minute.
28.8 million won a day.
This is so damn small.
Watch your head.
1st Floor gets 10.000 per minute.
14.4 million won a day.
This is so annoying.
I could've chosen the 8th floor.
No point regretting it now.
We chose the cards at random.
I didn't get much choice.
There were only two cards left.
You still managed to pick
better than I did.
And. you know…
What kind of show doesn't provide
such important information?
This should be illegal.
We should report it.
Still. you guys are so lucky.
I thought 10.000 won per minute was a lot.
Oh. 1st Floor.
I'm sorry.
We should've been more considerate.
Sorry?
Please don't be!
I wasn't trying to make you uncomfortable.
I was just unlucky.
I had other cards to pick from.
Besides. my legs are like this.
so I would've had trouble
with a higher floor.
I love the look on your faces!
Do you think this is funny?
That little…
What?
No one's in the wrong here.
Stop blaming each other.
It's not like we picked
the higher floors on purpose.
Today's cardio is done!
Whether you get 10.000
or 340.000 won a minute. in the end.
don't we all have the same goal?
Keep the show going
for as long as possible
and maximize our profit.
Isn't that our goal?
This is fucked. but he's right.
If you're all done whining.
shall we go eat?
Right. Let's all go eat now.
Come on. let's go.
The food and water.
How much will you send down?
It's crappy enough to get paid less
for being on a lower floor.
Do you want us to eat less too?
Well. no.
I thought of a way for us
to share the food equally.
May I explain?
Each person takes one meal kit.
From the 8th floor to the 1st floor.
one per person. which is fair.
They look so good!
This show puts us in an extreme situation.
Working as a community
is more vital than ever.
We need to unite as one
and trust each other.
That means there will be four left
after 1st Floor takes his.
What?
Why are we giving him four more?
No. That's not what we're doing.
Nobody will be left starving
if we each take one.
But if anyone wants more.
you can come down to the 1st floor
and share what's left.
A system where no one's at a loss.
Everyone has to give up a little.
but everyone can share the leftovers.
so no one loses out.
Naturally. this will build trust among us.
Have the seasoned ones.
-These?
-Yes.
Why?
'Cause it's hot.
-Are you finished?
-Eat up.
Yum. It's good.
Do you have any idea
what's in store for us?
Sorry?
We don't know what to expect.
so it's scarier.
Earlier. you said
you didn't know what to expect.
so you were scared.
Yes. I think I have a rough idea
of what they want.
-What's that?
-Hey!
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
We only have 15 minutes left!
Which one looks better?
She didn't buy them with time. did she?
Hey. If you want to buy clothes.
you should do it in your damn room!
Why fucking buy them out here?
Because if I do.
I can't wear them out here.
I want to wear them out here.
Why the swimsuit? There's no water.
-For tanning.
-You crazy bitch.
Do you have a death wish?
Talk it out. Don't intimidate her.
Is it because of this?
We can always extend that thing. Time.
How would we do that?
None of you know? Really?
How to extend it?
It's the stairs!
-The stairs?
-Yes.
There's a ton of stairs here.
The time extends whenever we step on them.
-Do you have proof?
-Proof?
Wait. What was it again?
Stop messing around and tell us.
I'll tell you if you apologize to me.
What?
I'll tell you if you apologize
for cursing at me before.
I'm so freaking sorry.
I apologize instead.
We have no time. Tell us already!
I guess that's a no.
You motherfucker!
Use your words.
-What's your problem?
-Just get it over with.
Can't you see everyone?
-No!
-I can't let it end like this.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity!
Who cares if she's wrong?
We have less than ten minutes!
-Okay.
-Let's give it a go.
For fuck's sake! Are you sure this is it?
It's still going down!
Less than 30 seconds left!
It's over? Just like that?
Back to 24 hours!
I told you. didn't I?
I told you it's the stairs.
That's what we've been doing.
To check out my room and everyone else's
and to get the meal kits?
I saw how the time extended then!
I'm pretty smart. aren't I?
Just like that.
we discovered a hidden rule.
Climbing stairs extends the time.
FOOD AND ACCOMMODATION PROVIDED
SPEND TIME TO EARN MONEY
IT'S NOT DANGEROUS
CLIMBING THE STAIRS EXTENDS TIME
I thought it was all over.
That was close.
Yes. I think I have a rough idea
of what they want.
Conflict. They want us
to fight each other.
Crises from the outside
will only make us cooperate and persevere.
But internal conflicts…
If we fall apart internally.
it's irreparable.
Yes. we need to stay united
through cooperation and perseverance.
Man. that 7th Floor is one smart guy.
I'll use this as long as possible
to avoid buying it again.
Three…
Two sheets should be enough.
It wasn't enough.
It pisses me off
the more I think about it.
I make 40 million every day.
I shouldn't skimp on things like this.
Don't chicken out. Just buy it!
Yeah. let's do it!
Excuse me. I'm gonna go big here.
Get me a portable toilet.
A simple one.
Yes.
Bring it.
I can't get a refund. can I?
That crazy bitch.
I can't believe she bought clothes.
It pisses me off.
Damn it. She's so annoying.
We did great.
This is all for us later.
Look how much money we made.
Okay. shall we get started?
STAIR CLIMBING
+210.000 WON
+20.000 WON
+30.000 WON
+50.000 WON
+340.000 WON
+80.000 WON
+130.000 WON
+10.000 WON
After learning
that stair climbing extended our time.
we climbed up and down
until our hearts were about to burst
and our legs were shaking.
The more time we gained.
the hungrier people got.
so the 1st floor became popular.
We were worn out every night.
but we couldn't complain.
I don't even feel like I've eaten.
Eating once a day
and nibbling on leftover food like this
is barely enough.
We go up and down those stairs
over and over every day.
It's all too harsh.
Even if the prices
were 1.000 times higher.
I'd like to buy some food.
-Like those hot dogs downstairs.
-I want burgers.
Fried chicken for me.
Let's split up.
We should divide our work.
So you want us to split into two teams
and climb the stairs every other day?
Yes. We can work one day.
then rest the next.
We'll give the leftover food
to the team that worked.
The working team can get two meals a day.
A single meal should be enough
on days off.
Yes. I agree with this.
One meal is enough when we're not working.
It's better to rest. isn't it?
I agree.
Same here.
Let's try it.
We'll see how much time we get.
How about we split up like this?
I'm switching teams.
We don't get along.
Me?
Is anyone willing
to switch teams with 2nd Floor?
The whiny chick. The thug.
The wacko.
THUG. WHINY CHICK
Who'd want to join that team?
The members speak for themselves.
Excuse me. I don't mind which team I'm on.
This is nice.
Two men on each team is perfect. isn't it?
Yes. this is great.
It was an excellent idea
to split into two teams.
Despite the hard work.
the prospect of resting the next day
is enough motivation.
And the best part is
you can eat to your heart's content
on the days you work.
"Those who do not work shall not eat."
-Are you okay?
-I almost hurt my back!
I'm sorry. 4th Floor.
-Whatever.
-I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry. Really.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Wipe that smile off your face
and get to work.
We're not gaining any time because of you.
What are you doing?
I'll fill in.
Sorry?
Get some rest. I'll fill in for you.
Any objections?
-No. I can--
-Forget it.
I feel stiff when I don't exercise.
I can…
How admirable.
THE NEXT DAY
You must be tired
from working two days in a row.
It's fine.
THE DAY AFTER
Should I help
or not?
Should I help or not?
Help? Or not? Should I help or not?
Should I help or not? Help or not? Wait…
Oh! Excuse me! Mr. 1st Floor.
Please go rest. 1st Floor. I'll do it.
Sorry. what?
Goodness. no.
-No. let me.
-I have to do it today.
Really. Look. I ate too much yesterday.
I'm having trouble digesting.
Yeah. so please go rest and recover.
Goodness.
I'm so sorry.
It's really fine.
Sorry. let me through.
Excuse me. Coming through.
God. we're all tired too.
We're all running
like our lives depend on it.
-Please have a seat.
-Sit here.
Shouldering extra work for a teammate.
How awesome am I?
I got this!
3rd Floor. You can't be here like this.
-Let's go.
-Wait. give me five more seconds.
Come on. Let's get up.
It's not…
Try to get up.
Gently. please. Yeah.
Please have a bite to eat.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
This way.
You're going to eat?
Sorry?
Are you actually gonna eat?
Come on. 4th Floor.
I mean. honestly speaking.
shouldn't 3rd Floor be eating instead?
Do you really need both meals
when you haven't even worked?
Think you're clever. don't you?
You have one extra
since 8th Floor doesn't eat anyway.
Why are you tripping?
I'm not saying you shouldn't eat.
You know? I was just saying it's not fair.
You should eat--
3rd Floor. please go on in.
You worked instead of me today.
-Sure.
-Don't be ridiculous.
You think we worked instead of you
for the fucking food?
You think he could eat this
with a clear conscience?
Am I wrong?
No. you're right.
Don't mind them. Just go eat.
They're just bitching
because they're fed up and tired.
Yes. she's right.
You should go and eat. 1st Floor.
It's just how it is.
No need to mind me. Yeah.
No. Please.
Go on. You should go and--
Come on. Just go in and eat.
-Thank you. 3rd Floor.
-Sure.
-No. still. he--
-Come on.
Just go eat. He said he was fine with it.
Are you okay?
Of course.
Because of this asshole.
I ended up coming
to this godforsaken place…
IN YOU. I TRUST
…and climbing a lifetime's worth
of stairs. you son of a bitch.
WEASEL
It's all your fault.
My legs.
Food is here.
What's all this?
Seriously. what the hell?
-3rd Floor.
-Yes?
Something fell. right?
I thought it was food.
but they sent down poop bags!
-For God's sake.
-1st Floor said to send them down.
I've given it some thought.
Since I'm not great at climbing stairs
and people keep filling in for me.
I thought of what I could do to help.
And. well…
1st Floor said he was torn up
about how he was impeding us
due to his condition.
I thought we'd be even
if you all sent down…
your waste bags to me.
Really?
While pondering what he could do
for the team instead of physical labor.
he said the delivery chute caught his eye.
It occurred to him that we could send
things other than meal kits through it.
1st Floor's proposal and our acceptance
established a sanitary worker among us.
When everyone fulfills their roles.
society reaches equilibrium
and functions smoothly.
And 1st Floor had found it.
A newfound self-value worth bartering.
Those less prone to hunger
share their food.
Get some rest.
I'll take it from here.
Those with fitter bodies
share their manpower.
Those who can't share those things
offer their space for communal use.
All in all. it's a pretty fair deal.
I'll see you later.
Hello. 1st Floor.
This will make it
more comfortable for you.
There's no need. We're fine.
Please do it later.
Are you done eating. 3rd Floor?
Not yet. I think I ate too fast.
I don't feel good.
I see.
What are you looking at?
The time…
It has been extending irregularly lately.
It shot up before midnight yesterday.
but now it has stopped increasing.
Do you think
it's because we're not climbing enough?
I'm not sure. Everyone's doing their job.
Did you see that?
We just got ten more minutes.
But everyone's taking a break
after the meal.
Did someone go up?
Fuck. What's wrong with that thing?
I told you.
They're getting stingier with time.
It's barely going up.
Do they want us
to ramp up the workload or what?
We're not Olympic athletes.
I'm over this.
-I'm sorry?
-What?
I'm not doing this anymore.
But we can't just stop working.
What are you doing?
It's not fun anymore.
Good luck. you three.
Just shut up and do it!
Why should I?
Hey. Shouldn't you be working harder
than the rest of us?
You make way more than we do.
Shouldn't you put in
a bit more effort than us?
Shouldn't you
and the people on the lower floors
work harder instead?
What?
Think about it.
You don't want to use your money.
so you've used our shared time
to buy toilet paper. wet wipes.
and other necessities.
Technically.
if we're using time to buy items.
aren't those on the top floors
paying far more than you guys?
That wacko…
After all. time is money here.
…isn't wrong.
An hour is only worth
1.2 million won to 2nd Floor.
but worth a whopping 20.4 million won
to 8th Floor.
Since we're using the time we share.
the higher floors
are technically spending more money.
I didn't take her as a thinker.
She's surprisingly sharp.
Let's keep climbing the stairs
instead of wasting time arguing.
The show's going to end at this rate!
Hey. let's climb with them.
We should help out.
Are you sure
climbing stairs gives us more time?
What?
It's strange.
We've been climbing the stairs
at the same rate.
That crazy bitch.
We've actually lost time
instead of earning it.
What if it doesn't go up anymore?
You're right.
We've been at this for over six hours.
We haven't earned a minute.
It'll be midnight soon.
so we must go to our rooms.
We can't do more today.
What? It just went up.
Hey. it just went up!
-Twenty minutes?
-Finally!
Wasn't that 20 minutes?
It must be lagging.
I guess it's working again now.
Hey. I knew it.
We were worried for no reason. I knew it.
-What a relief.
-Yeah.
I'm so glad.
I guess it'll go up.
even if it takes time.
It's midnight.
Let's all go in.
Great job today.
Let's go inside. Good work.
Everyone. come outside! Get out here!
I don't think we've been rewarded
our time. Hurry up. and come out!
Everyone. start running.
Everyone!
Let's run. everybody.
But we didn't even get our time
for yesterday's work.
What if it's of no use again?
Still. it's the only option we have.
Start climbing the stairs. everyone!
This is fucking bullshit.
-She fell on her back!
-4th Floor!
-What?
-She just--
Hold on.
-It's an epileptic seizure.
-What?
It's epilepsy! Don't touch her!
-Oh. epilepsy.
-Wait. we need to--
Do you have medical training?
-Yes. I was a nurse.
-Is there medicine for this?
She needs Phenytoin.
Stay where you are.
What are you saying?
Don't do anything. She won't die.
What?
Epilepsy doesn't kill.
Leaving her like this for so long
may damage her brain.
The medicine won't be cheap.
If we use up the little time we have.
the game is over!
You're not even human.
Don't get in my fucking way.
We need medicine for epilepsy! Phenytoin!
This is too funny.
Don't you see what I see?
Don't you all see that?
Forty hours?
This is so much fun.
It wasn't the stairs
that gave us more time.
Then what was it?
What. then?
What gives us more time?
It must be…
entertaining to watch.
PHENYTOIN
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org